This is a story about a lovely couple,
Rob and Elaine...
...who rented a house one especially
hot and sticky summer in the Hamptons.
Elaine invited her best single friends,
cindy and Janet...
...while Rob invited his single friends,
Ira and Matthew...
...to share the good times
and exorbitant rent.
Until one day,
this lovely couple had a terrible fight...
...when Elaine went for a run
and twisted her ankle...
...and came back early
to find Rob canoodling with Janet.
And cindy got tired of Matthew's
idiotic jokes and incessant market chatter.
Ira tried to be there for Elaine
and confessed his true feelings for her...
...which she tried to laugh off as a joke.
By August, it got to the point
where everything was so awkward...
...that nobody wanted to come back.
And that's when Janet
called her friend charlotte.
It's a really cute three-bedroom cottage.
They're giving us a fantastic deal
for the month of August.
Because it's haunted with
cheating boyfriends and sexual rejection.
We can always burn sage.
Sharing a house with your girlfriends
is fine in your 20s...
...but in your 30s, isn't it a bit pathetic,
like being the oldest kid at summer camp?
She has a point.
My 25-year-old assistant, Nina Grabowski...
...has a summer share in Bridgehampton
with 18 other girls.
They sleep in shifts.
- What if they meet someone?
- They fuck in shifts, too.
Hold it.
I can't believe you guys would pass up
a chance to get out of this heat.
Besides, the city's completely dead
during August.
- Because everyone's in the Hamptons.
- Or stuck in traffic trying to get there.
This could be the last summer we can all
get together and do something like this.
I mean, next year, who knows?
One of us could be married or have kids.
And we'll always regret that last summer
we didn't spend together in the Hamptons.
Charlotte's sweet hopefulness
touched something in all of us.
- Okay, I'm in.
- Me, too.
Fine, but I get the late shift.
Samantha always felt like
she was in her 20s...
...until seeing an actual twenty-something
brought her down to earth.
No, I'm getting you on the VIP list.
You have to try it for one night.
My best friend Jerry owns it.
He also owns the one in South Beach.
Yes, the same one.
Proof and confirm the guest list
for the Hetrick-Martin benefit.
And get me Richard Johnson, ASAP.
He is not a fag, because I happen to have
three friends he's personally fucked.
You are nasty. You are.
I'm sending you a car, to and fro, and if you
hate it, I'm gonna let you blow me. I am.
I am serious. Off, now.
Alec, I've gotta go.
I'll keep you posted, okay?
Bye, honey.
I have personal relationships of my own,
you know.
- Not with my clients, you don't.
- I have my career to worry about.
Your career is being my assistant.
You're so deluded. You wouldn't even
know what's hot if it wasn't for me.
Unfortunately you don't seem to
grasp the vast difference between us.
Yes, I do.
You stood in line at Studio 54...
...I stood in line at Studio 54, the movie.
I gave that bitch her first job out of
college. She didn't know a fucking thing!
Girls in their 20s, they're spoiled
and ungrateful. They think they're it.
Don't they realize, we're still it?
No, because the world validates
their delusion.
And she took a copy of my Rolodex.
Do you think I can sue?
- Do you remember us in our 20s?
- Dimly.
Have some compassion.
The only thing worse than being single
in your 30s is being single in your 20s.
Where've you been? I was worried
you'd miss the jitney.
The Hamptons Jitney is like
the bus to summer camp...
...only instead of singing everyone
ignores each other and talks on their cell.
Everyone, this is Greg.
This is Samantha, Carrie and Miranda.
Hi!
Greg's been going to the Hamptons
every summer for 20 years.
- Since I was six.
- You do the math.
I have.
Thank you.
Easy, sister, no need to push.
Four bumper-to-bumper hours later,
we arrived at our new digs.
They said this place was shabby chic,
I'm thinking it's much more shitty chic.
These towels are mildewed.
Actually, this whole house smells
like mildew.
It's not mildew, it's beachy.
Would you all stop being so cynical?
We're lucky to be here.
Cynicism. Now there's one advantage
we have over girls in their 20s.
I was cynical in high school.
Who's that?
It's Greg, that cute guy I met on the jitney.
I told him to drop by.
And if he asks, he thinks I'm 27.
Evidently, while we had taken
the Midtown Tunnel...
...charlotte had taken the time tunnel.
- Hi!
- Hey.
Come on in. You guys remember Greg.
Hi, Greg.
Hey!
Me and my housemates are having
a big bonfire tonight at the beach...
...and I just wanted to tell you
that you're all invited.
Excellent!
Here you go, ladies.
There's so much foam
you could ski on the head!
Sorry, it's been awhile
since I pumped a keg.
I love young men, but come on. The guys
here don't even have chest hair yet!
That's good news for their backs.
Sorry!
Okay, this is really fun.
How long do we have to stay?
God!
I'm gonna go tell Charlotte we're leaving.
Another thing about twenty-something
girls is they're very considerate.
You can always count on one of them
to hold your hair when you vomit.
Excuse me!
My God, Carrie Bradshaw!
- Yeah?
- Laurel Harris.
May I just tell you that I worship you?
I read your column every week,
it's like my religion.
Thank you.
I work in a publishing house,
but I'm really a writer.
- Great.
- We'll see.
Maybe I could send you something
to read sometime?
- Sure.
- That would mean so much to me.
To have someone like you as my mentor.
Well, mentor.
Could I call you sometime in the city?
If I could spend some time with you,
that would be so cool.
Of course. I'll be looking at
a very busy summer.
I can help.
I'll run errands, I'll do your wash.
No menial labor necessary.
I'll just give you my phone number.
My God, this is so cool.
Thank you.
- It's okay.
- Thank you.
The next day, Miranda woke up early
to enjoy the cool morning breeze...
...and a much-needed moment of solitude.
All right, somebody puked on the deck.
Sorry...
...Stacey and Holly did
too many Jell-O shots.
What are you, 25 now?
Good morning.
No, 27!
Whatever.
That week, back in the city,
I wondered what was the allure of the 20s?
On one hand, there's great skin tone,
the thrill of fresh experience...
...and the sense of a consequence-free life
full of endless possibilities.
While on the other, there are horrible
apartments, sexually inexperienced men...
...and embarrassing errors
in fashion judgment.
Should we fear these freshly minted, single
women as a threat to our very survival...
...or pity them as clueless half-wits
about to get their dreams dashed...
...and illusions shattered?
Twenty-something girls...
...friend or foe?
And that evening,
in my first act as a mentor...
...I took my young acolyte to a book party.
My God.
I can't believe I'm out with
Carrie Bradshaw. This is too cool.
Stop, I can feel my head swelling.
If it gets any bigger,
I'll have to say goodbye to my hats.
I have a question.
Do you think that 25 is too young
to write a personal memoir?
As long as it doesn't deal with incest,
Prozac, or partying, no.
It does deal with sex,
or rather not having sex.
It's about how girls my age
are saving themselves for marriage.
- Saving what for marriage?
- Our virginity.
Are you telling me that you've
never had sex with a man?
That is correct.
Okay, what do you consider sex?
Are you implying I'm
some kind of Lewinsky?
I'm not! I'm talking no blowjobs,
no hand jobs.
All right, I get it, no jobs of any kind.
You know what?
I think I need to get a drink.
- I'll get it. Cosmopolitan, right?
- Yeah.
I remember from your column.
A 25-year-old virgin was getting me
a cosmopolitan.
The generation gap
had never seemed so wide.
Hi.
- Have you actually read the book?
- No, have you?
Not yet.
Know anything about the author?
His family has a history of diabetes
and he has a steel splint in his left femur.
- I'm his doctor, Bradley Meego.
- Carrie Bradshaw.
My doctor won't even make house calls,
let alone attend a book party.
I've never been to one.
I thought it might be interesting.
It's exceeded all my expectations.
Generally, it's cheese and crackers.
You never see an actual shrimp.
No, I meant you.
I'd ask you for a drink after
but I'm driving to the Hamptons.
I'm going out to the Hamptons tomorrow.
Great, can I call you there?
All right, you know what?
I'll be with my friends Saturday
at Townline Beach.
A big yellow umbrella.
You can come by and say hello.
Is this a ploy to see me in my bathing suit?
- Here's your Cosmo.
- Thank you.
Dr. Bradley Meego, this is Laurel.
- Hi.
- Hey.
What if it rains?
Do we pick another date?
Doctor, you are persistent.
All right. In case of emergency, only.
Now I'm gonna have to buy the book.
Nice meeting you. You, too.
Drive safe.
My God, he is such a fox.
Did you meet him when I was at the bar?
Lady, you've got it going on!
That Saturday turned out
to be hot and sunny.
While we sat under our umbrella...
...twenty-something girls sizzled on the
sand like rotisserie chickens.
Excuse me,
when did tanning come back in style?
Hand me the 45!
Forty-five, I didn't know
it went up that high.
You could sit in a microwave and not burn.
It's Charlotte's,
but I don't think she'll be using it.
It's not good for her 27-year-old image.
She actually put on oil.
Just let her have her fun now.
Come Labor Day, she's gonna look like
a 27-year-old handbag.
I'd risk a few precancerous
freckles for a summer romance.
And right then, my summer romance
made his appearance, right on schedule.
Yellow umbrellas seem to be
very popular this year.
This is Dr. Bradley Meego.
Hello.
What kind of a doctor are you, Doctor?
Internal medicine.
General, all-purpose kind of thing.
Fabulous, so you can prescribe medication?
- What'd you have in mind?
- Feel free to ignore her.
I'm sure that's impossible.
I'm gonna go take a quick dip.
- You promise not to ditch me, now.
- I promise.
- Is that the guy from the book party?
- Yeah.
I've got to start reading.
He's cute. I'm just not
really sure I'm interested.
Good-Iooking, polite,
house in the Hamptons.
- It's good on paper.
- You know the rule.
Good on paper, bad in bed.
A "good on paper guy"
is a guy with great credentials...
...who you always end up leaving
for some hot guy...
...who rides a motorcycle and doesn't have
a checking account.
My God!
The water feels so awesome.
You guys should really go in.
You better put on some sunscreen,
Georgette Hamilton.
That's okay, I never burn.
Well, I do.
In fact, I've had enough for today.
I'm gonna go grocery shopping.
You guys want anything?
We should get some rum.
We can make Long Island Iced Teas.
Yes, I love Long Island Iced Teas.
Excellent!
I took a leap of faith
and made reservations...
...at one of those impossible-to-get-into
restaurants for tonight.
I'd love to...
...I just can't abandon my friends.
Actually, that wasn't an invitation.
It was just restaurant chitchat.
I'm kidding.
How about after dinner?
I've got a great little house,
cute porch we could sit on.
I don't know.
Okay, how about I just call your...
...in-case-of-emergency number
this weekend.
The emergency being,
I think I'm gonna miss you.
Yes, you could definitely do that.
Good.
Romantic, polite, and his very own house
south of the highway.
My good-on-paper guy
was jumping right off the page.
Later that afternoon, we came back from
the beach rested, rejuvenated...
...feeling almost 29 again.
Even Miranda was in good spirits.
Guys, I just got back from the market.
Fresh corn and seafood for dinner.
Except, your groupie can't stay.
I only got enough for the four of us.
She's here?
Yeah, she was asking too many inane
questions. I sent her up to your room.
- Thanks.
- Sorry.
I've got to shower, the sand is itchy
in my bathing suit, and then I'll help you.
Take your time. That came for you.
My God!
What's wrong?
It's for the Hamptons Hoedown
tomorrow night...
...and the event is being run by
Nina G. Public Relations. Nina G!
Overnight, Samantha's ex-assistant,
Nina Grabowski...
...had reinvented herself as Nina G.
I was up for that job and now she's using
my Rolodex to put together the guest list.
While Samantha was getting
fucked royally by her protege...
...mine was giving me the royal treatment.
It's not that I don't wanna
have sex with men...
...I feel like these previous
generations of women have...
...devalued sex to the point
where it's not even special anymore.
One summer, when I was 15,
I read everything Jackie Collins ever wrote.
I thought to myself, who cares?
Is it supposed to be shocking...
...wagging one's pussy
at every good-Iooking stud who walks by?
- Please.
- And what is it you like about my column?
I have a tiny tick on my stomach,
and I can't get it off.
- Does it hurt?
- No, but it itches.
My God, that is not a tick.
What is it?
There go our shitty sheets.
My God, it's so disgusting.
- Where's she going?
- To the drugstore.
Charlotte really is in her 20s.
She's got crabs.
My God!
That night, I called Dr. Meego.
I figured it was an emergency.
I have this thing about crabs.
I had them in college
and it scarred me for life.
I can't go back to that house
until the mattresses are sanitized...
...and the sheets and towels are burned.
I'm flattered you thought of me.
I'd be happy to prescribe your friend
some industrial-strength pubicide.
She can take care of herself.
Cheers.
You might have to spend the night here.
I might have to, but only to sleep.
Women always say that
and as soon as the lights go out...
...boom, they're going for my pajamas.
All righty. I promise, no funny stuff.
That night we slept together,
but we didn't sleep together.
It was really nice.
I believe it was the first instance of a case
of crabs moving a relationship forward.
Every year, one of the local
Hamptons billionaires got down and dirty...
...and threw a big hoedown
full of cowboys and caviar.
It was the event of the season.
We joined Samantha
to lend our moral support.
I can't believe it.
There're people here who don't even come
to my parties and they came to Nina's.
Look at her over there.
Beef jerky carpaccio?
I am just so depressed right now.
Excuse me.
Where are you going?
To congratulate Nina.
I may need her to hire me someday.
While Samantha set out to negotiate
twenty-something detente...
...charlotte prepared to launch
a full-out war.
Excuse me.
Do you know that you gave me crabs?
- What?
- You heard me.
- What makes you think it was me?
- That is so tacky.
So is lying about your age.
I saw your license
when you bought the beer.
I didn't lie. You made an assumption,
I didn't contradict it.
Whatever.
I may have given you crabs,
but you deceived me.
- That is so much worse.
- Grow up.
You are a waitperson.
That doesn't mean wait, it means go!
My God, you actually came.
I just stopped by to wish you good luck.
It's a fabulous party.
That is very cool of you.
I told you not to seat Martha
near the hayride. She's allergic.
Please try to keep the young people
out until after 11:00.
We're all out of country-fried goat cheese,
somebody got stuck with a cactus needle...
...and there are people outside
who aren't on the list.
Jesus fucking Christ.
You are totally coked out.
You are totally jealous.
My God, what is that?
What is that sound? My God!
That's not supposed to happen until 12:00.
- I know.
- This is your problem. Get them to stop!
I can't, they're on a fucking barge!
Could you help me?
I need to get everybody outside.
I'm totally fucked right now.
Okay, people, fiesta fireworks, outside!
Let's go!
This is Greg.
I think the two of you
would really hit it off.
Hi.
I began to realize, that the biggest threat
twenty-something girls posed...
...was to themselves.
I've been looking all over for you.
- Look, I got one just like yours.
- That's great.
You want me to get you a Cosmopolitan?
No. I'm gonna go find my date.
But I'll see you later, okay?
That guy from the bookstore?
My God, he was so cute.
Annoying, yes. Dangerous, no.
They were simply our youthful
doppelgangers...
...who needed our compassion
more than anything.
And then everything I so firmly believed
was promptly blown to pieces.
Is it you?
Hey. What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
What are you doing here?
I just got back this week from Paris.
This is Natasha.
Hi. It's a pleasure to meet you.
I've heard so much about you.
Really?
Natasha's parents have a house in East
Hampton. We came up for the weekend.
Excuse me. It's nice to meet you.
I'm sorry, I'm just a little stunned here.
And confused.
Who is she?
I meant to call you.
She's this girl that I met in Paris.
She works for Ralph Lauren in Europe.
You're in from Paris for the weekends?
No. The Paris deal fell through.
I planned on calling you.
I certainly didn't want
to run into you like this.
You can't plan everything.
Life can be pretty random.
I'm here on a date, too, somewhere.
He's a doctor, Bradley Meego.
He's good on paper, probably like Natasha.
Good-Iooking, sweet, blah-blah-blah.
How old is she, anyway?
I don't know, 26, 27.
Something like that.
I'll see you in the Hamptons
or back in the city.
I promise to call
when I get back into town.
Are you okay?
No, I just ran into Big.
He's back from Paris.
He has a new girlfriend.
She's 26.
- Where is he? I didn't see...
- God.
And then I realized...
...twenty-something girls
are just fabulous...
...until you see one with
the man who broke your heart.
欲望城市
（性爱专家凯莉布雷萧）
’二十岁女孩VS三十岁女人’
这是关于一对爱侣
罗伯与伊莲的故事
在一个特别炎热的夏季
他们在汉普顿租了一栋别墅
伊莲邀请她最好的单身朋友
辛蒂和珍娜
而罗伯也邀了单身友人
艾拉和马修
一起共度美好时光
以及分摊过高的房租
直到有一天
这对爱侣起了激烈的争执
伊莲因慢跑时不慎扭伤脚踝
提早返家
发现罗伯和珍娜一起泛舟
辛蒂厌烦马修的白痴笑话
以及没完没了的市场经
艾拉则对伊莲示爱
她却试图一笑置之
到了八月，情况变得很尴尬
没人想再回到那个地方
珍娜便在此时打给夏绿蒂…
那是栋小巧的三房别墅
正适合八月去度假
-那屋里充斥求欢被拒的阴影
-我们可以烧鼠尾草
二十多岁时和女性友人
分租房子还说得过去
但到了三十几岁仍如此
不会有点可悲吗？
她说得有理，我25岁的助理
夏天在布里治汉普顿
和18个女孩一起分租房子
-她们得轮班睡觉
-要是有艳遇怎么办？
-连做爱也要排班
-慢著
我不敢相信
你们要放弃避暑的大好机会
再说，八月时
整个纽约就像死城
因为人人都去了汉普顿
或者正塞在去那里的途中
这或许是最后一个
我们能自在出游的夏天
明年，谁知道呢？
我们其中一人可能已结婚生子
我们会终生遗憾最后一个夏天
未能一起在汉普顿共度
夏绿蒂充满希望的甜蜜语气
打动了我们
-好吧，我加入
-我也是
好吧…
但我要排晚班
莎曼珊永远觉得
自己还是二十几岁
直到她看见
真正二十几岁的女人
你得尝试一次
屋主是我最好的朋友杰瑞
他在南滩也有一栋房子
确认宾客名单
然后尽快帮我联络理查强森
他不是同性恋
我三个朋友跟他上过床
你真下流
我已经把邀请卡寄给你了
如果你不喜欢，尽管找我算帐
我是说真的，马上去办
艾力克，我得挂了
有最新消息我再通知你
我有自己私人的人际关系
-不准勾搭我的客户
-我也要烦恼我的前途
你的前途就是担任我的助理
要不是我
你哪懂甚么东西才热门
妮娜，你似乎不明白
我们之间有著天壤之别
我当然明白
你站在夜总会门口排队
而我站在电影院门口排队
那臭丫头大学毕业第一份工作
是我给她的
二十几岁的女孩真是不知好歹
她们以为自己多了不起
-她们不懂我们仍是主流吗？
-这世界支持她们的错觉
她还拿走我通讯录的副本
我能告她吗？
-记得我们二十几岁那时吗？
-没甚么印象
唯一比三十几岁单身还惨的事
就是二十几岁时孤零零一个人
你们差点赶不上巴士
它就像开往夏令营的游览车
只不过谁也不理谁
自顾自地讲电话
各位，这是葛瑞格
她们是莎曼珊、凯莉和米兰达
二十年来
葛瑞格每年夏天都去汉普顿
-从我六岁起
-你来算年龄吧
-我算过了
-谢谢
别急，小姐，没必要推挤
在车阵中缓慢前进四小时后
我们抵达了新住处
他们说这房子有点简陋
我认为是糟透了
这些毛巾发霉了
整个房子都有霉味
那不是发霉，是砂砾
你们别再冷嘲热讽了好吗？
我们能来这里就很幸运了
愤世嫉俗，这是我们胜过
二十几岁女孩的优势
-我高中时就很会挖苦人
-是谁来了？
是葛瑞格
我在巴士上认识的那个帅哥
我叫他过来坐一下
如果他问起，就说我27岁
当我们穿越城中隧道来到此地
夏绿蒂已穿越了时光隧道
快进来
你们还记得葛瑞格吧？
你好，葛瑞格
我和我室友今晚要在沙滩
办一个盛大的营火派对
-你们都被邀请了
-太棒了
各位，拿去吧
泡沫好多
简直可以在上面滑雪了
我已经很久没用唧筒了
我爱年轻小伙子
但这里的男人连胸毛都没有
这对他们的背部是好消息
抱歉
真是有趣极了
我们还要待多久？
天啊
我去跟夏绿蒂说我们要走了
二十几岁的女孩非常体贴
当你呕吐时
她们会帮你把头发撩起来
不好意思
我的天，你是凯莉布雷萧？
我叫萝拉哈里斯
我一定要告诉你我有多崇拜你
-我每个礼拜都读你的专栏
-谢谢
我在一家出版社当助理
但我其实是个作家
也许改天我能把我的文章
寄给你看看吗？
当然可以
你不知道能有像你这样的人
做我的良师意义多么重大
-良师…
-回城里我能打电话给你吗？
我能跟你见面吗？
当然，不过这个夏天我会很忙
我可以帮你跑腿、洗衣服
不需要干仆人的活儿
我把电话号码给你
-我的天，真是太酷了
-谢谢
隔天，米兰达一早起床
享受清晨的微风
以及更为必要的独处时光
-有人在门口呕吐
-抱歉
史黛西和荷莉喝太多酒了
你以为你现在几岁，25吗？
早安
-不，27岁
-随便
回到城里
我纳闷二十多岁的魅力是甚么
气色很好
对新奇的体验感到兴奋
不计后果
充满无限可能的人生
同时住很糟糕的公寓
交往没有性经验的男友
以及穿没有品味的衣服
我们是否该担心
这些年轻的单身女子
对我们的生存造成威胁？
或者同情她们
幻想即将破灭却一无所知？
二十多岁的女孩
是朋友…还是敌人？
那晚，身为良师的第一件事
我带著我年轻的门徒
参加一个新书派对
我的天
我真不敢相信
我和凯莉布雷萧一起出现
够了，若我的头继续变大
我就必须和我的帽子道别
我有个问题，25岁写回忆录
会不会太年轻？
只要里面没提到乱伦
百忧解或狂欢就不会
它探讨性
或者应该说是没做爱
它是关于我这年纪的女孩
为了婚姻保有处女之身
-为了婚姻保有甚么？
-贞操
你的意思是
你从没和男人上过床？
没错
你认为性是甚么？
你在暗示我跟莒恩丝基一样？
不，我是指口交、手淫都不算
我懂了，任何费力的事都不算
你知道吗？
我想我需要喝杯饮料
我去拿，四海为家，对吗？
我记得…你专栏中写过
一个25岁的处女
正帮我去拿四海为家
世代鸿沟从未显得如此深远
-嗨
-你读过这本书了吗？
-还没
你呢？你对作者有何认识？
他的家族有糖尿病遗传
而他左股骨上了夹板
-我是他的医生，布莱德米哥
-我是凯莉布雷萧
我的医生平常连电话都不打
更别说是来参加新书派对
我想这可能会很有趣
现在已经超出我的期望了
通常，连只真正的虾子也没有
不，我是指你
等会我很想约你一起喝东西
但我要开车去汉普顿
事实上，我明天也要去汉普顿
太好了，我可以打电话给你吗
星期六我跟我朋友
会去唐莱海滩
寻找很大的黄色遮阳伞
你可以来打个招呼
这是为了看我穿泳衣的计谋吗
这是你的酒，小姐
他是布莱德米哥医生
她是萝拉
万一下雨怎么办？
要另外定约会吗？
医生，你还真是不屈不挠
好吧，除非有急事才打
现在我得买下这本书了
很高兴认识你，你也是
小心开车
他真迷人，你是在我去吧台时
认识他的吗？
小姐，真有你的
那个星期六炎热又晴朗
当我们坐在遮阳伞下时
二十多岁的女孩
像烤肉般发出嘶嘶声
请问古铜色皮肤
何时又开始流行了？
-把防晒系数45的拿给我
-我不知道有出到这么高系数
你可以待在微波炉中而不灼伤
这是夏绿蒂的
但我不认为她会用
这不符合她27岁的形象
她竟然还抹了油
到时候，她看起来
便会像个27岁的手提包
我愿意为了夏日恋情
甘冒长癌症雀斑之险
就在此时
我夏日恋情的男主角
准时出现了
黄色遮阳伞今年似乎非常流行
嗨
莎曼珊、米兰达
这位是布莱德米哥医生
你是哪一科的医生，大夫？
甚么都看，可以说是万事通
太棒了，那么你能开药方？
-你有甚么意见？
-别理她
我要去冲个澡
你保证不丢下我？
我保证
他是你在新书派对上认识的？
我得开始阅读了
他很可爱
我只是不太确定有没有兴趣
人长得帅、又有礼貌
在汉普顿有房子
擅长理论
你知道那定律
擅长理论的人床上功夫很差劲
擅长理论的男人
拥有出色的背景资历
最后你却永远会为了一个
骑摩托车的浪子离他而去
海水真是棒呆了
你们应该下去玩一玩
你最好擦一点防晒油
-没关系，我从来不会晒伤
-我会
我要去买点东西
你们想要甚么吗？
兰姆酒，我们可以做长岛冰茶
好，我爱死长岛冰茶了
太棒了
我在一家很热门的餐厅订位了
我很想去
但我不能就这样丢下我的朋友
其实这并不是邀请
我只是随口提起
开玩笑的
那晚餐之后呢？
我们可以在阳台上坐坐
我不知道
好吧，这个周末
我打你的紧急电话如何？
紧急状况是
我猜我会开始想你
好，你当然可以这么做
浪漫、殷勤
加上他在公路南方拥有的房子
这个擅长理论的男人
正从纸上一跃而出
我们从海滩返回别墅时
感觉彷佛又是29岁般年轻
连米兰达心情都很好
我刚从市场回来
晚餐有新鲜的玉米和海产
你的崇拜者不能留下来，凯莉
我只准备了四人份
她在这里？
她问太多问题了
我让她去你房间
-谢了
-对不起
我得把身上的沙冲乾净
然后就去帮你
慢慢来
莎曼珊，那封信是你的
-我的天
-怎么了？
明晚是汉普顿的土风舞晚会
由妮娜Ｇ公关公司举办
一夜之间，莎曼珊的前助理
便将自己重新塑造成为妮娜Ｇ
她用我的通讯录制作宾客名单
当莎曼珊被她的手下
狠狠摆了一道
我的门徒正给我女王般的待遇
不是我不想跟男人上床
但以前的女人贬低了性的价值
因此它甚至不再特别了
我15岁时
我读每本杰姬柯林斯的作品
当时我在想
「这应该是惊人的吗？」
「对每个经过的性感男人
搔首弄姿？」
你到底喜欢我专栏哪一点？
我肚子上有个虱子，我弄不掉
-会痛吗？
-不，但会痒
-我的天，那不是虱子
-那是甚么？
-都是可恶的床单害的
-好恶心
-她要去哪里？
-去药房
夏绿蒂真的回到二十几岁了
她身上有阴虱
当晚，我打给米哥医生
我想这算是紧急情况
我大学时长过一次阴虱
害我一辈子留下疤痕
我得等床单和毛巾都烧掉
才能回去
我很高兴你想到了我
我很乐意为你朋友
开一点杀菌药
我想她能照顾自己
乾杯
你可能得在这里过夜
-可能，不过只是睡觉而已
-女人总是这么说
灯一关掉
她们就来脱我的睡衣
我保证没有滑稽的玩意儿
我们同床，但并未上床
那感觉好极了
这是第一件
阴虱让感情有所进展的案例
每年，本地的有钱人
都会办一个挤满牛仔
和鱼子酱的盛大土风舞会
这是社交季的大事
我们陪莎曼珊出席
给予她精神支持
有人不参加我办的派对
却参加妮娜办的
你看看她
来点生腌牛肉乾？
我现在真的非常沮丧，失陪
-你要去哪里
-去恭喜妮娜
有一天我可能得靠她
赏我一口饭吃
当莎曼珊出发去向
二十多岁的女孩低头
夏绿蒂则准备发动战争
不好意思
你知道你把阴虱传染给我吗？
-甚么？
-你听到了
-你凭甚么认为是我？
-那真是太低级了
你谎报年龄还不是一样
昨晚我看到你的驾照了
我没有说谎
是你这么假设，我没反驳而已
也许阴虱是我传染给你的
但你欺骗我
-这严重多了
-成熟点吧
你是个接待员
没做好份内事就滚吧
我的天，你真的来了
我只是来祝福你好运
-这是个很棒的派对
-你真好
我不希望玛莎乘乾草卡车
她会过敏
你能让年轻人一直到11点
都待在外头吗？
羊酪已经没了
还有人被仙人掌刺到
外面有不在
宾客名单上的人要进来
-你办事能力真差
-你太小心眼了
那是甚么？我的天啊
那是甚么？
那应该等到午夜才放的
-我知道
-这是你的问题
-叫他们停下来
-不行，他们在该死的游艇上
莎曼珊，你能帮我吗？
我需要让大家到外面去
我现在把一切都搞砸了
各位，外面在放烟火
我们往外移动吧
妮娜，这是葛瑞格
我想你们两个将会一见如故
我发现二十多岁的女孩
所造成的最大威胁
是对她们自己
我到处找你
你看，我有条跟你一样的项
-那很好
-你要来杯四海为家吗？
我要去找我的男伴了，待会见
那个在书店认识的男人？
他好帅
她们的确烦人，却不危险
只不过是我们年轻时的翻版
需要我们的同情甚过一切
接著我所坚信的一切马上瓦解
-是你吗？
-你怎么会在这里？
我怎么会在这里？
那你又怎么会在这里？
我刚从巴黎回来
凯莉，这是娜塔莎
很高兴认识你
我听说许多有关你的事
是吗？
娜塔莎的父母在这里有栋别墅
我们只是周末来度假
抱歉失陪，幸会，凯莉
对不起，我只是…有点震惊
还有困惑，她是谁？
我本来想打给你
她是…
她是我在巴黎认识的女孩
她在欧洲替劳夫罗伦工作
所以你只是
从巴黎回来度周末？
不是
巴黎的计划已经告吹
我…我有打算跟你联络
我真的不想
在这种情况下遇见你
世事难料
我的男伴也在这里…某个地方
他是布莱德米哥医生
他擅长理论，或许跟
娜塔莎一样，好看、温柔…
她到底几岁？
我不知道，26、27
大概吧
我们在汉普顿或回纽约时再见
我保证回城里一定打电话给你
凯莉，你还好吧？
不好，我刚碰到大人物了
他从巴黎回来
交了新的女朋友
她26岁
他在哪里？我没看见他
我这才明白
二十多岁的女孩确实很迷人
直到你看到她身边
有个曾令你心碎的男人